Alfonso Torres

GAME DEVELOPER

Work Experience

GAME DEVELOPER

2AwesomeStudio | 02/2023 - Present **Consoles Porting**

- Use and management of the SDKs and GDKs provided by Play and
- Optimization of blueprints and code in projects for consoles.
- Implementation and management of TRCs and XRs.
- Maintenance and improvement of projects for consoles.

GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMER

Pendulo Studios | 02/2022 - 02/2023

Tintin Reporter: Cigars of the Pharaoh

- Use of Unreal Engine 4.
- Development and console-oriented basics.
- Engine feature development and implementation.
- Development and implementation of gamplay tools and mechanics in
- Use of blueprints as scripting language to implement game levels.
- Research and implementation of RBFs system in Unreal.
- Multidisciplinary development coordinated with other departments such as animation, design and art.

UNITY DEVELOPER

Research Group - UPM | 05/2020 - 08/2020

- Migration of source code from Phyton to C#.
- Development and design of a planetary system simulator with different parameters and configurations.
- Integration of new functionalities within the system.

Education

MASTER'S DEGREE IN VIDEO GAMES **PROGRAMMING**

U-TAD | 2020 - 2021

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY OF MADRID | 2016 - 2020

Technologies and skills

Languages:

- C
- C++
- C#
- Java
- LUA SQL

- Unreal Engine 4
- Unity 3D
- Visual Studio
- Jenkins

Tools:

- GDK Microsoft
- SCE Play

Technologies:

- OpenGL
- Git
- SVN

Others:

- JSON
- XML



Summary

After several years of personal and professional development in various companies, I would like to expand and find new challenges to help me evolve. To fit into an ambitious project with which to share illusions and objectives.

I am a self-taught person, organized, with companionship and with a great motivation able to adapt to any project.

My main goal is to create products that add value to people's lives.

Contact

- Madrid, España
- +34 675 87 15 00
- alfonsotorres.schz@gmail.com
- /alfonsotorresschz
- AlfonsoTorres369
- Alfonso369
- draxnar.itch.io
- Portfolio

Languages

- English (B2)
- French (B2)